10% DHT liposomal cream and um he asked
if it would be interesting to add that
next to the trt cream what's your
opinion on
that I've been triing this personally um
I've just finished up using it for a
couple of months I wanted to tral it
myself before I uh made any comments or
recommendations on it what I found was
that adding any amount of additional DHT
cream to uh the existing 20% transcrotal
testosterone cream I was using uh
induced low estrogen side effects it
hurt my joints uh quite quite profoundly
um and I tried you know different dosing
you know one click a day up to four
clicks a day adjusting the Baseline
testosterone dose to be able to
accommodate more DHT I think you get so
much DHT conversion already from the
transcrotal cream that it's just not
necessary and it pushes that equation I
think into an unfavorable Direction I
think that if there was going to be
potential use for the DHT cream it could
be used topically uh after a period of
PFS where there is actually damage to
the vascular Network in the penis um the
studies on DHT cream topically at the
moment uh the only one that's been done
topically on the penis was regarding
micr penises during our development um
to help achieve proper growth with that
so I think theoretically it may help and
apply to guys who've had PFS but I think
if anyone was going to use it it would
be more beneficial to add it to a
injectable testosterone protocol because
the amount of DHT that we're already
getting via the transcrotal cream I
think is already well beyond what we
need so I haven't found it to be too
useful and um I think if people are
wanting to optimize their cream protocol
and I'm just going to give a shout out
to Keith here because this 100% came
from him he shared with me a huge
catalog of data from the HRT base of
cream I think if people aren't using the
HRT base and they're using the liposomal
I think swapping over to the HRT base of
cream is what's going to make the
biggest difference it's also a much more
natural gentle cream less preservatives
in it as well people are even apparently
using it just as a moisturizer without
any actual hormones in it because it's
such a good cream um so I think if
people want to optimize their cream
protocol it would be looking at swapping
to the HRT base yeah well I asked
um Nicholas plas from NP laabs about it
and he said he had to order it and it
would take three months to get an HRT
base I'm hoping that with the clinic
that I'm setting up that we will have
such a high demand for it that we will
make it worthwhile for him to have it
available uh all the time because the
liposomal cream is great I mean we we
probably both use the same liposomal
product from MB Labs I've just found
that some guys need three four clicks
twice a day to get a optimal level of
testosterone I remember when I reviewed
your blood work a while back and we did
the video you know publicly about it um
a lot of guys are needing double that
dose that you're using to get those
levels with the liposomal but then when
they use the HRT base they don't need
that um Keith showed me some fantastic
results where guys were getting
astronomical numbers and having to
reduce to just one C twice a day to get
into that sweet spot that we like to sit
in so um yeah hopefully that's something
that they're going to make readily
available because I think that we're
going to have quite a big demand for it
for them